<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>commissions on Mat the Printer</title>
    <link>https://mattheprinter.github.io/tags/commissions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in commissions on Mat the Printer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mattheprinter.github.io/tags/commissions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Niveau 1 - Tattoo Flashday</title>
      <link>https://mattheprinter.github.io/niveau-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mattheprinter.github.io/niveau-1/</guid>
      <description>Level 1 This project was a collab with my favourite local tattoo artist (from Dijon 🇫🇷). I was asked to provide a flash sheet, which theme was entirely free. So i went with that old tabletop RPG vibe that i love, inspired mostly by John Blanche, amongst other famous 80&amp;rsquo;s concept artists.
I decided to go with it and create 6 flashes, straight from the players handbook. Each design represents an item, spell or creature any 1st level player could encounter during its journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Niveau 1 - Tattoo Flashday</title>
      <link>https://mattheprinter.github.io/niveau-1bis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mattheprinter.github.io/niveau-1bis/</guid>
      <description>Level 1 This project was a collab with my favourite local tattoo artist (from Dijon 🇫🇷). I was asked to provide a flash sheet, which theme was entirely free. So i went with that old tabletop RPG vibe that i love, inspired mostly by John Blanche, amongst other famous 80&amp;rsquo;s concept artists.
I decided to go with it and create 6 flashes, straight from the players handbook. Each design represents an item, spell or creature any 1st level player could encounter during its journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Din Djaarin in Jango&#39;s suit</title>
      <link>https://mattheprinter.github.io/djaarin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mattheprinter.github.io/djaarin/</guid>
      <description>Din Djaarin in Jango&amp;rsquo;s Suit This project was a personal tattoo project to continue my patchwork sleeve.
It represents Din Djaarin, better known as Mando. When the show went out, i immediately identified as him, as most fathers did, i guess.
This mandalorian reference displayed as a fatherly figure and not as a warrior is absolutely intentional. Din Djaarin doesn&amp;rsquo;t bear weapons here, only the space coffin of the child he is devoted to, in a posture that reminds of those of St Mary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imposter syndrome goblin</title>
      <link>https://mattheprinter.github.io/imposter-syndrome-goblin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mattheprinter.github.io/imposter-syndrome-goblin/</guid>
      <description>Imposter syndrome goblin This project was a personal tattoo project to continue my patchwork sleeve. This goblin stands for the imposter syndrome that seem to hit all of us artists
The design is inspired by Saint Barthelemy, depicted as he died : skinned to death, carrying his own skin and the knife of his torturer.
The goblin is a figure of self acceptation: we all are goblins from time to time, ugly, stressed, powerless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thornwood Parfums</title>
      <link>https://mattheprinter.github.io/thornwood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mattheprinter.github.io/thornwood/</guid>
      <description>Thornwood Parfums This project was a commission from a NZ brand in the fragrance game. They wanted to develop a strong artwork line, invoking the heavy designs from the gothic medieval era, that i love and try to put forward.
Thornwood wanted 5 woodcuts that evoked a specific mind state. Just as if you could describe an olfactive impression with words. Difficult, innit? Well i did exactly that with feelings and linocut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Of Thrones Fan art &#39;#1</title>
      <link>https://mattheprinter.github.io/game-of-thrones-fan-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mattheprinter.github.io/game-of-thrones-fan-art/</guid>
      <description>The technique The sketch was originally drawn on transparent paper, then reported on the lino block, then inked on the block. Once dried out, the block was carved with gouges: the linocut process itself. This process was particularly long, due to the massive amount of texts that is included in the orginal poem.
This was one of my earliest projects, one of my biggest occasions to learn and do mistakes. My skill level when i started was nothing close to the one i had when i finished it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
